LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now. Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
Hello everyone!
Welcome to the Laughing Man Room!
Well well, to think he'd return after
six years in hiding...
It's pretty surprising, eh?
I certainly was surprised.
Though it might be inappropriate,
considering the circumstances,
as the net master, Onba, I felt my blood stir.
Those here right now are
diehard Laughing Man "freaks".
But they also have no intention
of entering the debate.
Stop talking like that.
You'll get... attacked... in the comments...
I heard that there'll be
people here in this chatroom
who'll be discussing interesting
things about the Laughing Man.
Who among you would that be?
I think all of us here would fit the description.
Although there are those who
don't quite meet the criteria.
What is that supposed to mean?
Just what I said.
The Man
Who Lurks
In The Net's
Dark Depths
In any case, what's this about the Laughing
Man dying right after he reappeared?
I was just starting to hope that I could
become one of the real-time freaks, too.
What are you getting worked up about?
No one's complaining about
things like that anymore.
How idiotic.
Speaking of "idiotic", I think that your
appearance qualifies in that category.
Well, hurry up and give us
a topic worth discussing.
All right then, why don't we discuss why the Laughing Man
suddenly reappeared and made an assassination threat?
Allow me, teacher.
I think it's because the world
continues to be boring and full of crap.
We know that already.
What I'm trying to get at is,
could it be that this incident and the incident
six years ago were perpetrated by different men?
"Men"?
You don't even know if the
Laughing Man is actually male.
The Laughing Man is a he.
According to information from a particular
source, he has to be a man.
Besides, if the person was female,
would she call herself the "Laughing MAN"?
Wait, please.
I think you'd realise this if you'd
look closely at the available data.
The person has not referred to
himself as the Laughing Man even once.
Even so, he's a man!
Remember that broadcast when he
kidnapped the company's president?
He definitely looked like a guy.
That's easy to explain.
He could have been wearing a male cyborg body.
Wait a second, you're going off topic here,
don't you have any thoughts on how this incident is too different
from his past "style", which was limited to corporate terrorism?
Although this incident also started from
suspicions over a micromachine company,
don't you think that it was too crude of him to plunge
headlong into an assassination attempt on the Commissioner?
Well, as the story goes,
it's true that he started off six years ago
by hacking into the cyberbrains of the president's
secretary and family members sending emails.
Then, are you saying that this recent
incident was perpetrated by a fake?
Isn't that a strong possibility?
It's been a full six years
since he last disappeared.
Isn't this incident just a farce that rode on the waves
generated by the Laughing Man's surging popularity on the net?
But what is the basis behind the belief that
corporate terrorism IS the Laughing Man's style?
Wasn't his first kidnapping also "crude"?
Well, I don't think he did anything on
impulse after kidnapping the president.
That's right...
After all, it wasn't cool at all to
manipulate someone else to assassinate others.
Well, the Laughing Man is
thought to be a Grade A+ hacker,
but he's never killed anyone.
Heh, it was fun to see,
but I guess it was all a fake.
I guess it's better that way...
So much for being a real-time
Laughing Man freak...
Poor you.
Then... what are you reasons for
thinking that the Laughing Man is "cool"?
Well, of course he's cool!
How can you say that he isn't
after all the things he's done?
I'm not saying that he's NOT cool.
If someone is "cool" for being a good hacker,
then it's true that the time-delayed virus
used in the incident was certainly a marvel.
After all, it was made so well
that not even the police could create a vaccine
until after it became active in
the Security Police's cyberbrains.
That's true enough.
After all, it's even rumored that the police couldn't
even find a trace of the virus itself after the incident.
I see.
Still, the perpetrator ended up dead.
Yeah!
Since the guy that made the
virus was killed by someone else,
it has to be that the guy was
fake and he ended up being killed.
By whom, and for what reasons?
Allow me, teacher.
It was because of some
conspiracy by a secret society!
Come to think of it,
according to information I got
from this particular source,
the victimized corporations had hired
assassins even before this incident.
Which "sauce" did you get it from?
Note: He's making a pun out of "source" and "sauce"
which have identical pronunciation in Japanese
Pork cutlet? Oyster?
Why would the corporations get rid of him?
Well, they've been waiting
for a chance all this time!
They had cause to go after him after
all the threats and ransom demands.
They finally tracked him down when he made
that assassination threat, that's all.
Even so, what's the point in
getting rid of an imposter?
That's right.
Even if he was the real thing,
there's no way that they could've first found
someone that not even the police could identify.
Th-that's exactly what makes it out of character for him!
It's not very "cool" to be
tracked down so easily like that.
Then, how about this: he was
killed by the real Laughing Man.
Of course that can't be.
Just as the police say,
the reasonable conclusion is that
the Laughing Man was a complex entity
that had some internal squabbling.
If so, then can it be said that
we're back to our first conclusion?
That is, that the recent incident was
instigated by a different "person".
I'll ask this again,
what is the basis behind the belief that
corporate terrorism is the Laughing Man's "style"?
You're to obsessed with this!
It's because he wouldn't
be "cool" otherwise, okay?!
But... please try to remember.
Was the first incident all that "cool"?
I see!
We have to go back to the beginning
if we are to properly discuss this!
All right then,
let's look back on the Laughing Man Case
as a little break from the current debate.
It is now 7:20 AM on February 3rd,
Travellers Weather
Forecast
time for the traveller's weather forecast!
To all of you who're commuting to
work this morning, my best wishes.
Today's Weather
Today, February 3rd, is just 100 days from
the opening of the International Exposition.
So, for today’s poll,
we've thought of this question:
2024 International Expo Japan
100 days until opening of the Awaji Expo
Expo...
That's unfair!
If so, then please tell the
truth in front of the camera!
Stop this. You can't shoot.
Do you really think so?
Watching this is probably a bit boring now,
but we can't really help that,
since this was the only time someone who
might have been the man himself was seen.
If that promise you made a while ago is
true, then right here and now...
Have you noticed?
I can't do that right now.
The programme's logo was overwritten with his mark.
It's incredibly detailed work, don't you think?
Why don't you tell them?
That won't have any meaning!
Yeah, not to mention the regional
weather forecast symbols.
SERANO-San, unless you speak the truth yourself...
Although, there are rumours that that stuff changed
only after they started broadcasting replays.
Whatever the details were,
this is the origin of the Laughing Man
Case, that shook the nation six years ago.
But he's not cool at all in that footage.
His hands were trembling when
he was holding the gun, too.
You simpleton!
That's what's cool about him!
Still, if you compare this with the
subsequent corporate terrorism incidents,
his actions were really rash.
That's not it.
It's because he put himself in
the danger in the beginning,
even though he was a Grade A+ hacker,
that we felt sympathetic.
We felt that he was trying to lay bare
the falsity of scheming corporations...
I don't get it.
Nah, that's what it is.
While seemingly instigating
an overly-simple crime,
the cunning indicated by
hacking all the media sources...
That's where his charisma lies.
You guys are so passionate.
It's like, "I love the Laughing Man", you know?
It's not like he actually sent out
that message himself, even once.
In addition to SERANO Corporation,
it now seems that Japan Micromachine
Corporation has been threatened.
Special Emergency Report
The Laughing Man Strikes Again!!
This is most alarming news!
Could those be an unknown number of office desks?
This time, it is a threat made against Sagawa
Cybernetics Corporation's main division!
How in the world did he manage to move
all those desks in a single night?!
It can surely be said that this is an
unprecedented case of corporate terrorism!
Is he real?!
The Cybernetic Man: Part II
He has to be real, right?
Please call the Nanoplant Corporation.
I mean, Satsuma Meditech is the largest
corporation of its kind in Kyuushuu, right?!
Why would you send a killer
virus into a place like that?!
I have no idea!
He probably hacked into the
gardener bot last night and did it.
Take the helicopter out!
Hey, look!
Oh, I have a t-shirt with Mytel
Corporation's mystery circle printed on it.
After this, when it was
decided to invest public funds
in order to offset public fear over the devaluation
of the victimized corporation's stocks,
the Laughing Man announced
that he would cease his attacks
and disappeared into the dark depths of the net.
I remember that Kadoya once
temporarily raised its stock price
by saying that there was a Laughing
Man symbol in its snack products.
What do you think about the rumours
that certain individuals made huge profits
using the stocks of all those corporations?
If we were to base our judgement solely on that,
then it's quite possible that the
Satsuma Meditech case was a fake.
Is that a cute girl's intuition?
Well, why don't you try comparing the shift
in stock values for other victimized companies
with that of Satsuma's?
Well, come to think of it,
Satsuma was the only one that didn't
receive government assistance.
I see.
No one noticed, because all six corporations
profited by about the same amount,
after the ceasefire was announced.
Well, it's true that even the talk show where
the threat was made felt pretty lame.
Well then, it's decided.
It was all staged by the media.
Now that we're reflecting on this anew,
the incident of six years ago seems to
have a lot of inconsistencies as well.
I guess it would be a little too forced
to think that these attacks
were all by a single person.
So, in the end, it means that it
was carried out by a group, right?
There are quite a few critics out there
who think that the mindset behind the
first and second bout of incidents differs.
I want to push for a "single perpetrator" theory.
That's a bit difficult to
stomach, don't you think?
There's no point in trying to figure out whether the
two incidents were perpetrated by the same person.
I feel that the key to unlocking this case
actually lies in the factors
that lead to a chain of events
after both the kidnapping six years ago,
and the recent assassination threat.
Oh, that's pretty sharp, lady!
I think so, too.
All right then, let's think it over,
while looking over the visual
files we have in stock here.
However, before we proceed,
we'll delete the backup
files cached on the server,
so let's take a short break.
Hey, do you remember how
the alleged designer of this mark, Paul,
got taken in for questioning by the
task force at the time of the attacks?
The one who kept saying that
his design database got hacked,
and that the particular design was stolen?
Yeah, although it's true that he consequently
was able to become a famous designer.
I respect his abilities as well.
In any case,
I wonder what the reason was behind the
huge popularity of this case at the time.
The mystery that seemed easy
to understand, yet was not,
and sensational events kept
happening, with excellent timing.
You do say intelligent things sometimes.
The fact that Serano's president wasn't exactly
cooperative also fell into that area, didn't it?
It's still suspected that he made
a deal with the Laughing Man, too.
Still, what spoke to me the most
was the heroic mentality and solitary
image presented in the first incident.
Yeah, for me too.
This recent incident started during the press
conference over the interceptor's illegal use,
but was that also an indication
of a "heroic mentality"?
And, it was none other than Serano Genomics
itself that developed the interceptors in question.
Don't you feel that there are some
connections to those in power?
Just as I thought, this is very interesting!
How should I say it? A one-hundred-million-strong
nation of detectives?
Basically, it results in a mass parallelization of the spectators!
How about this: everything was self-scripted and
self-acted farce by the micromachine industry,
and the Laughing Man was a "program" designed
to manipulate stock values from the beginning.
That's too boring!
The Laughing Man does exist!
Maybe you just want him to exist.
But according to information
I obtained from my source...
Heh, "source" again.
This incident generated two hundred
billion dollars in the economy overall.
That's a pretty good raison
d'etre, wouldn't you say?
Everyone, since you all don't seem to want
to join in on my discussion very much,
I'll now present a special tidbit of
information I got from my own "source".
The police's official report that the simultaneous
multiple failed assassination attempts
were all due to the virus that
Nanao-A unleashed is a lie.
On what basis?
Yeah, identify the source of that information!
"Source" yet again.
By the way, how many times
has JD used the term "source"
since he arrived in this chatroom?
I'm curious myself.
To tell you the truth...
At the time, I'd hacked my way
into the scene of the incident.
Are you serious?
Then, are you saying that you were also
thinking of attempting an assassination?
N, no, that's not it. I was just peeking in
because I wanted to know what would happen.
So, I think that the other
39 people who were caught
were not being manipulated by the virus
and were just there of their own free will.
There were other hackers just like me.
I think that there may be those in the
audience who tried to crack in as well.
Although... everyone else seemed to be
failing in their attempts for some reason.
Did you... see it?
If that were true, it would be a huge scandal.
We wouldn't be able to trust anything.
So that's it?!
I'd also thought of going to
the ceremony hall that day!
Dammit...
Hey, wait a minute.
Then, isn't it possible that the Laughing
Man was among the 39 who were arrested?
I don't think so.
Those who were caught were either
passionate fans like us or mimics.
Then, you're saying that those people went there
in response to Nanao-A's assassination threat?
It's not exactly that...
I actually have another piece
of special information...
I was net-diving after the incident occurred
and I found a server registered under Nanao's
name that had been overwritten by him.
That is the one.
You're right!
Please be careful.
It is guarded by firewalls
with offensive capabilities.
If you dive in there at Level Six,
you'll see that there are many
simulations of plans left in there.
Renewed threats to micromachine heavyweights...
There is also plan to target the
cyborg food industry, as well.
All programs have a common point:
their success hinges on a
delayed fragmented virus.
But after that, there was one question left.
Nanao's commissioner assassination plan
doesn't actually exist among the simulations.
While having so many meticulous plans on hand,
why did he suddenly move to
assassinate the commissioner?
You've done good research.
It's all I do, so...
But, why?
Are you trying to say that
Nanao-A was yet another mimic
who was affected by the assassination threat?
There is no other way to explain
why he threw out the rest of
his carefully constructed plans
and used his ace-in-the-hole on
a careless assassination plan.
Who was the one who made the
assassination threat, then?
You're trying to read too much into this.
Let's try to decipher something more substantive.
Still, doesn't his story seem pretty plausible,
after being shown something like that?
Well, let maeask you this, then...
Why was it that there were no other
cybernetic attacks aside from Nanao's
despite the fact that many others were caught
trying to assassinate the commissioner?
It could be that only Nanao was
supposed to attack that day.
And, it was already predetermined
that he would fail and be caught,
thus also making him the perpetrator behind
the Laughing Man Case, six years ago.
Who would benefit by creating such a scenario?
That would be, of course, the pol...
H, hey...
You've been creating some
pretty roundabout explanations,
but you've got it figured out to a good degree.
Did you see my sacrificial firewall?
W, were you by any chance that lady
who was pinning down the Security Police?
Well?
Yes, I was watching.
That firewall was quite dangerous.
Do you have a fragment of it?
Yes... This is it.
Thank you.
You're welcome...
May I ask you a question, too?
I thought at first that the
Police were behind it all.
But that offensive firewall was clearly
different from the police's firewall
that was set up throughout the ceremony hall.
I've never seen such a firewall...
Then, it WAS the Laughing Man, after all...!
As a sign of my thanks for giving
me that fragment, let me warn you:
If you know too much,
you'll end up getting wiped out in real life.
Hey, did you get disconnected or something?
No, I'm all right.
I'm sorry but I think I'll
excuse myself for the day.
What are you saying?
You haven't finished what you were saying.
I'm sorry about all that.
Geez, what was that about?
It all feels lame all of a sudden.
Wait, not that getting worked
up in a place like this
would let us get any closer
to the heart of the matter.
Who knows?
The real Laughing Man could
be watching us right now!
You're already too far gone
if you're thinking that.
Nonetheless, this case is just all too difficult.
We're all going to get tired of it eventually.
I think that the Laughing Man is a
phenomenon that was created as some symbol
by something random that was given
birth to by this corrupted world.
Even this group,
which is being lead around in circles,
is already a mimic.
Still, even if all of this was
nothing but a random phenomenon,
just as that "Babe Ruth" guy said,
I do feel that there are some commonalities
between the first kidnapping incident and
the assassination threat six years later.
I feel that only those two specific incidents were
executed by perpetrators possessing the same ability.
With regards to the scope, goal, and mentality,
the others were but copies
created in the hero's absence.
Although it is quite doubtful that the perpetrator
behind the two incidents is the "original".
Lady, you're a sharp one!
Is this a forced transfer?
What is that?
Hey, why?
We're at a good point right now.
Can't we stay connected a bit longer?
You miser!
So, yeah. What do you think?
Dammit... I couldn't trace him.
Hey.
What, did you say something?
Were you actually net-diving all this time?
God, you're so dangerous.
Eh, I can drive in my sleep around here.
Well, what was it?
Forget it.
I'm not going to say it again!
A phenomenon created by
mimics without the original...
Two pieces that don't fit into that picture...
What are you talking about?
Nothing.
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up